In days of legend,
在传说的日子里, 众神行走在凡间...
and tormented mortals.
折磨凡人.
Athena, goddess of warfare and wisdom,
雅典娜, 战争与智慧女神...
but chose to protect us.
但是选择保护我们.
Brave young knights from across the globe
来自全球的年轻勇敢圣斗士...
swore their allegiance to her.
对她宣誓效忠.
They learned to harness Cosmo...
他们学会了驾驭宇宙能量...
the power of the stars.
...星辰之力.
Their fists cracked to the heavens
他们的拳头砸向天空...
in battles against those who wished Athena dead.
对抗那些希望雅典娜死的人.
Over time...
随着时间的推移...
the gods retreated and became myths.
众神退却, 成为神话.
But then, 18 years ago,
但是, 18年前...
Athena was reborn as a helpless child.
雅典娜重生为无助的孩子.
A knight clad in gold armor
一名身穿金盔甲的圣斗士 为保护她而献出生命...
And that's how I found her, lying in his arms.
这就是我找到她的方式, 躺在他的怀里.
A mortal girl with the power of a god.
一个拥有神力的凡人女孩.
Since then,
从那时起...
I've been searching for a new generation of knights
我一直在寻找新一代的圣斗士...
to protect Athena and the Earth.
以保护雅典娜和地球.
We fight to protect ourselves.
我们为保护自己而战.
But we also fight to protect each other.
但是我们也为保护对方而战.
There's always something bigger than you, Seiya.
星矢, 总有比你更重要的东西.
You'll have to fight to protect that as well.
我们也必须为保护它而战.
You give up?
你投降了吗?
Never!
永不!
Nice try. But not tonight.
想得美, 但今晚不行.
-Tap out. -No!
-投降. -不!
You must learn when to quit!
你必须学会何时投降!
Never!
永不!
No, Seiya! Don't!
不, 星矢! 不要!
Promise you won't come out.
-答应我你不会出来. -我答应.
Hey, kid!
嘿, 孩子!
Come on, you're up next.
来, 下一个到你.
You win this fight, maybe you get a shot at me someday.
赢了这场, 也许有一天你能跟我对打.
Hey! Listen to me.
嘿! 听我说.
No more of that dancing around, you understand?
不要再到处乱跳, 明白吗?
You make it a good show this time.
-这一次给我打好来. -天啊.
Fight this time, asshole.
这次给我认真打, 混蛋.
It's time for the main event!
重头戏时间到了!
Introducing first, the undisputed champion of the Octagon.
先介绍一下, 八角擂台无可争议的冠军.
Give it up for Jaki the Beast!
掌声鼓励野兽扎击!
Jaki! Jaki! Jaki!
扎击!
And the contender, who literally danced his way
对手是...
let's hear it for Street Kid Seiya!
让我们掌声鼓励街童星矢!
You both know how this works.
你们俩都懂得它的方式.
You know the rules. There are none.
你们懂得规则. 就是没规则.
Anything goes until one of you gives up or blacks out.
打到其中一个投降或昏迷.
If you give up, you're banished from the Octagon.
如果你投降...
Understood?
明白吗?
Damn it, fight!
该死的, 打!
What, you think you can just ignore me?
你以为你可以不听我的话吗?
Okay, calm down, big guy.
冷静, 大家伙.
Ballet's over, kid.
芭蕾结束了, 孩子.
Cassios wins.
卡西欧斯赢!
Every...
每.
single...
一.
time.
次!
Cassios! Cassios! Cassios!
卡西欧斯!
You give up?
你投降了吗?
Yeah!
好!
You don't know when to quit, huh?
你不懂得何时投降.
Yeah.
是的, 我以前听过.
We're not done here!
我们还没结束!
This ain't over!
这还没结束!
Come outside.
出来.
You're cute, but you're not my type, man.
你很可爱, 但是你不是我喜欢的类型.
There's someone outside that wants to speak with you.
外面有人要和你谈.
He knows about your search.
他知道你的搜寻.
He knows what you're looking for.
他知道你在找什么.
Give me that.
给我.
Yeah, it's me.
是我.
Think I found one of your Cosmo guys.
我想我找到你其中一个宇宙人了.
I'm out of here.
我要离开这里.
Your little show in there made some people upset.
你在那里面的表演令一些人不高兴.
Look, I'm not looking for trouble.
我不是来找麻烦的.
You may not be looking, but you've found it.
可能你并不在找, 但是你找到了.
In a few moments, Vander Guraad will be here with her boys.
多一会, 范德古拉德将和她的人在这里.
Who?
谁?
My ex-wife.
我的前妻.
She controls this fighting ring.
她控制这格斗擂台.
It's her recruitment operation.
这是她的招募运作.
What does she recruit?
什么意思? 她招募什么?
Warriors with special skills.
拥有特技的战士...
For her private army.
加入她的私人军队.
Okay.
-好. -我看到你在擂台上的表现.
I knew it had to be you, Seiya.
我就知道一定是你, 星矢.
Who are you?
你是谁?
I'm the only friend you have.
我是你唯一的朋友.
You need to make a choice, Seiya.
你必须做出一个选择.
Come with me or try your luck against Guraad's warriors.
跟我来或试图对抗古拉德的战士.
Lead the way.
带路.
Come on!
来吧!
Look what we've found.
看我们找到什么.
What are those guys made of?
那些人是什么东西做的?
You don't want to know. Keep moving!
你不想知道. 继续走!
Our ride's just around the corner!
我们的车就在转角处!
Get down!
趴下!
Meet Mylock, my assistant.
介绍你迈洛克, 我的助手.
Those guys work for your ex-wife?
那些人替你的前妻工作?
Surrender the boy!
交出那男孩!
Dude, you gotta make better life choices.
你必须做出更好的人生选择.
What the hell is that thing?
那是什么?
Hope you had a light dinner.
希望你吃了一顿清淡的晚餐.
Why are they after me?
他们为何要捉我?
They're after warriors with a strong Cosmo.
他们捉拥有强宇宙能量的战士.
Cosmo? Is that a new martial arts or something?
宇宙能量? 那是新武术之类的吗?
You should know. You tapped into it in the Octagon.
你应该知道. 你在擂台时触动了它.
I didn't tap into anything. They got the wrong guy!
我没触动到任何东西! 他们找错人了!
Oh, would you like us to stop and let them know?
你要我们停下来让他们知道吗?
God!
天啊!
Hold on tight!
抓稳!
I am not going another step until you tell me what's going on.
除非你告诉我发生什么事, 否则我不会再走一步.
There'll be time for that later.
以后会有时间的.
We're still in danger.
-我们还有危险. -你真的...
Okay, okay, okay. Go to sleep.
好. 去睡吧.
Hey. Hey. Wake up. Wake up.
嘿. 醒醒.
Wake up. Come on.
醒醒! 起来!
You need to hide. No matter what happens, you stay out of sight.
你必须躲起来.
I have to make sure these people don't find you.
我必须确保这些人找不到你.
Promise you won't come out.
答应我你不会出来.
Okay. I promise.
好. 我答应.
Thank you.
谢谢.
For what?
为了什么?
You tapped into your Cosmo.
你触动了你的宇宙能量.
No, Seiya. Don't!
不, 星矢!
Led me right to your doorstep.
带领我到你家门口.
Saved me so much trouble.
省了我很多麻烦.
Let's go!
走吧!
You can't use it. Only the Pegasus can!
你不能用它. 只有天马可以!
That's why you're coming with us.
所以你要跟我们来.
Relax.
放松.
Relax, we're safe now.
放松, 我们现在安全了.
Safe?
安全?
First I get attacked by ninja cyborgs,
首先被忍者机械人袭击, 然后被一艘宇宙飞船射击...
And then that freak in a suit drugs me!
然后那个穿着西装的怪胎给我下迷药!
Allow me to rephrase it.
请允许我重新措辞.
You're safer here than with Guraad.
你在这里比和古拉德一起更安全.
She has already captured many kids like you,
她已经捉了很多像你这样的小孩, 吸干他们的宇宙能量.
Stop talking nonsense and tell me what's going on!
停止胡说并告诉我真相!
-Prepare for landing. -What?
-准备降落. -什么?
You might want to buckle up.
你可能要扣上安全带.
No, I want answers now!
不, 我马上要答案!
Oh, shit.
糟了...
I said, you might want to buckle up.
我说过你要扣上安全带.
You couldn't just tell me this thing lands vertically?
你就不能告诉我这东西能垂直下降吗?
Let's start afresh, shall we?
让我们重新开始, 好吗?
My name is Alman Kido.
我叫阿尔曼基多.
Once upon a time, I was a businessman.
我以前是商人.
Mylock, let her know our guest has arrived, please.
迈洛克, 请通知她说我们的客人到了.
Yes, sir.
遵命.
I won't hide the fact I've been quite successful in my trade.
老实说, 我的生意蛮成功...
But the one thing money can't buy is purpose.
但是有件东西钱是买不到的, 那就是目的.
So this is where you store your "purpose"?
这里就是你收藏"目的"的地方?
Yes.
是的.
Tell me, Seiya, what do you see?
告诉我, 星矢, 你看到什么?
A whole bunch of real old stuff, I guess.
一大堆很古老的东西?
I see stories.
我看到故事.
Ancient heroes were defined by their monumental deeds
古代英雄由他们不朽的事迹定义...
as much as by their tragic ends.
就像他们悲惨的结局一样.
I always admired the formidable magnitude of their fate.
我一直很钦佩他们命运的艰巨性.
I envied it. I used to think the ancient lore held no secret for me.
我很羡慕它.
I'm afraid that was my hubris.
但恐怕那是我的狂妄自大.
What do you know about Athena?
你对雅典娜了解多少?
-She was a god of war. -And wisdom.
她是战神.
What if I told you Athena had returned in human form
如果我告诉你 雅典娜以人类的形式回来了...
and you are destined to become one of her guardian knights?
而你注定要成为她的守护圣斗士之一?
I'd say your therapist isn't worth his paycheck.
我会说你的治疗师不值他的薪水.
Things happen for a reason, Seiya.
事出必有因, 星矢.
Your Cosmo brought you here.
你的宇宙能量把你带来这里.
Actually, I was brought here on a very expensive aircraft.
其实我是被一架很昂贵的飞机带来的.
And now I'm leaving on my own two feet.
现在我要靠两条腿离开.
You know the truth in your heart, Seiya.
你心里知道真相, 星矢.
Your sister knew it too.
你姐姐也知道.
What do you know about my sister?
你知道我姐姐什么?
Ten years ago, Guraad detected a strong Cosmo
10年前...
What did she do to her?
她对她做了什么?
I don't know, but your sister gave herself up
我不知道...
She knew what you were to become.
她知道你将成为...
A warrior of Athena. The Pegasus Knight.
雅典娜的战士...天马圣斗士.
The Pegasus Knight?
天马圣斗士?
You're really out of your mind.
你真的疯了.
Guraad is after her too.
古拉德也要捉她.
Your mission is to protect her.
你的任务是保护她.
I can take care of myself.
我可以自己照顾自己.
Why would I ever want to risk my neck to protect some rich girl?
为何我要冒着性命危险保护富家千金?
Because our little Sienna here is the reincarnation of the goddess Athena.
因为我们这位小西耶娜...
-Dad. -Don't you have something for our guest?
爸...
Sure, a toilet, so he can flush himself out.
当然. 一间厕所, 好让他可以被冲出去.
Wow, spoken like a true goddess.
哇, 像女神那样说话.
Dad, come on. This moron can't seriously be the Pegasus Knight.
爸, 拜托.
Go on.
去吧.
Fine.
好.
You might recognize this, Seiya.
你可能会认得这个, 星矢.
This is Patricia's.
这是属于派翠西亚的.
That is the key to the Pegasus armor.
这是你开启天马盔甲的钥匙.
Without it, you don't stand a chance against Guraad's army.
没有它, 你没机会打败古拉德的军队.
I could've handled those guys.
-我能应付那些家伙. -迈洛克可不是那样说.
So how's this supposed to help me find my sister?
这个如何帮我找到我姐姐?
You give me a little present and expect me to help you out?
你给了我一份小礼物就期待我会帮你?
My plan is to trust you to do what is right.
我的计划是相信你做正确的事.
And what would that be?
是什么?
I suppose you've never heard of Marin, the Silver Knight.
我想你从未听说过马琳, 白银圣斗士.
God, another one of your old legends?
你的另一个传说?
Marin can teach you how to reveal
马琳能教你如何揭开...
the hidden secret of the pendant.
吊坠隐藏的秘密...
So you can protect Sienna, and yourself, against your enemies.
这样你就可以保护西耶娜 和自己免受敌人的伤害...
And maybe even help you find your sister.
甚至能帮你找到你的姐姐.
Ancient gods. Magic knights.
远古神灵. 魔法圣斗士.
Do you have any idea how totally insane you sound?
你知不知道这听起来有多疯狂?
I know, it is a lot to take in, isn't it?
我知道, 一时很难接受, 对吗?
So why don't we have breakfast, take the day off and...
不如我们先吃个早餐, 休息一天...
Well, I am hungry, but...
我饿了.
A goddess's fate is on the line, but sure.
一位女神的命运岌岌可危, 但是, 当然...
Let's eat pancakes.
我们吃薄煎饼吧.
Yeah.
好.
Get off my ring, you scum.
离开我的擂台, 混蛋.
Get out of my ring!
离开我的擂台!
You moron.
你这笨蛋.
You were supposed to keep a low profile.
你应该保持低调.
And I did.
我做到了!
We need to shut this place down.
我们必须关闭这里.
-You don't get to decide that! -That's right. I do.
-由不得你来决定! -对. 是我.
Guraad, come on.
古拉德, 拜托.
We have a great partnership.
-我们的合作关系很好. -是的.
How's the boy's Cosmo?
那男孩的宇宙能量怎样?
It's legit.
真的.
Good news. I've got a new deal for you.
好消息.
No ring, no deal.
-没有擂台就没得谈. -更好的.
Nobody needs a loser who gets his ass kicked by a scrawny kid.
没有人需要一个被瘦皮猴打败的失败者.
He got a lucky break.
他只是幸运.
No man gets lucky twice with Cassios.
遇上卡西欧斯, 没有人能幸运两次.
I can beat anyone, anytime.
我可以随时打败任何人.
Well, let's see if that's true.
让我们拭目以待吧.
Something wrong?
怎么啦?
I just don't know how you can breathe while you're eating like that.
我只是不知道你这样吃东西的时候如何呼吸.
Where I come from, you eat as much as you can, when you can.
在我老家, 有机会吃就尽量吃.
You never know where your next meal's coming from.
你永远不会知道下一餐是什么时候.
You wouldn't understand.
你不会明白...
Rich girl.
富家千金.
No, I wouldn't.
不, 我不会.
But I'm sorry you had to live like that.
但是我很抱歉你必须这样过活.
Sir. There's an urgent call.
先生, 有个紧急电话.
Please excuse me.
失陪了.
So...
那么...
How does it feel to be a goddess?
成为女神是什么感觉?
Well, I'm not a goddess yet.
我还不是女神...
Just Sienna.
只是西耶娜.
But her Cosmo is getting stronger by the day,
但是她的宇宙能量一天比一天强大...
and someday soon I will become Athena.
很快地我就会成为雅典娜.
Most people would be excited
大多数人会很兴奋...
to have breakfast with a future goddess.
和一位未来女神共进早餐.
Guess I'm not most people, then.
我猜我不是那大多数人.
Well, then maybe you should--
好吧, 也许你应该...
Maybe I should what?
也许我应该什么?
You should back off.
你应该退下.
Jeez, don't be so sensitive.
天啊, 不要那么敏感.
Just get away from me, okay?
-只是...远离我, 好吗? -好, 抱歉如果我...
Hey!
嘿!
Dad!
爸!
-Are you okay? -Wait!
-你没事吧? -等一等!
What's going on?
发生什么事?
She could kill you right now.
她现在可以杀了你!
I'm here, sweetheart, just relax.
我在这里, 亲爱的, 放松!
What just happened?
发生了什么事?
She bears a goddess's Cosmo in the body of a mortal.
她的凡人身体里承载着女神的宇宙能量.
When our sensors detect a potential Cosmo burst,
当我们的传感器检测到 潜在的宇宙能量爆发时...
the building automatically blocks the signal.
建筑物自动屏蔽信号.
It's the only way we can keep Sienna hidden from Guraad.
这是我们让西耶娜 不被古拉德发现的唯一方法.
Which is why I am stuck here like a prisoner.
所以我像囚犯那样被困在这里.
Excuse me.
对不起.
Wait. Wait, so... So you really are...?
等一等, 那你真的是...?
You really think this guy could beat the Pegasus Knight?
你真的认为这家伙能打败天马圣斗士?
Perhaps. If we give him the prototype.
也许...如果我们给他原型.
Next candidate?
下一个候选人?
You giving up already?
投降了吗?
What the hell are you made of?
你是什么做的?
Disengage.
停止!
We ain't done yet.
我们还没结束!
You made your point, Cassios.
你证明了你自己, 卡西欧斯.
You're a strong man.
你是个强悍的男人. 但是你只是个男人.
I have a problem.
我有一个问题.
His power's a liability.
他的力量是一种负担.
Once he learns to control it, no living man will be able to stop him.
一旦他学会控制它...
What, you think I could, though?
什么, 你认为我可以吗?
You know, with your prototype thing?
用你的"原型"东西吗?
I have a good ear.
我的耳朵很灵光.
So, what's your price?
那你的代价是什么?
Well, that depends.
那可要看情况.
Can I kill him?
我可以杀他吗?
That's kind of the point.
这就是重点.
I'll do it for free.
我免费做.
-You all right? -I'm better.
-你没事吧? -我好多了. 你呢?
It's just that I can't believe you really are a--
只是我无法相信你真的是一位...
A goddess?
一位女神?
I'm never gonna call you that.
我绝不会那样称呼你.
So how do people usually react when they learn you're Athena?
当人们得知你是雅典娜时通常会有什么反应?
Varies.
各式各类.
Like, the day after I was born, someone tried to kill me.
例如我出生那天, 有人想杀我.
No.
不.
Not even you could annoy someone that much in just one day.
你不可能在一天内惹恼一个人.
I was told a knight in gold armor gave his life to save mine.
有人告诉我, 一个身穿金盔甲的圣斗士为了救我而牺牲.
When they found him, he was still holding me in his arms.
他们找到他的时候, 他还搂着我.
Who found you? Alman?
谁找到你? 阿尔曼?
And Guraad.
还有古拉德.
Though she was a little more into the gold armor.
虽然她对金甲更有兴趣.
Used it to develop technology far beyond anything you could imagine.
用它来开发远远超出你想象的技术.
Look at the bright side.
往好的方面想.
Half your foster family is great.
你一半的寄养家庭很棒.
When Alman's around you, he almost looks like a real dad.
当阿尔曼在你身边, 他看起来就像真正的父亲.
Alman is my dad, and I love him more than anything in the world.
阿尔曼是我的爸爸, 我爱他超过世上一切.
Although that might be hard for you to understand, street boy.
对你来说可能很难明白...
I do.
是的.
I had someone like that once.
我曾经有过一位这样的人.
Your sister?
你姐姐?
What was she like?
她是什么样子的?
She was kind.
她很善良.
And strong.
和强壮.
And protected me when I couldn't protect myself.
当我不能保护自己时, 她保护我.
And you won't stop until you find her.
你不会停止直到找到她.
I will someday become Athena.
有一天我会成为雅典娜.
I don't have a choice.
我没有选择.
But that doesn't mean you have to become the Pegasus Knight.
但是那不代表你必须成为天马圣斗士.
Alman said it's my destiny.
阿尔曼说这是我的宿命.
Nobody's destiny is written in stone.
没有人的命运是注定的.
Except yours.
除了我们.
Your Cosmo bursts,
当你的宇宙能量爆发...
do they come with visions?
你会看到东西吗?
You have visions too?
-你也看到东西? -为什么重要?
Cosmo visions are a window into the universe.
宇宙观是通向宇宙的窗口.
They can show us things.
它们可以让我们看到东西.
So that Silver Knight your dad mentioned...?
你爸说的那个白银圣斗士...?
-Who, Marin? -Marin.
-谁, 马琳? -马琳.
Do you think if he could teach me to control my Cosmo,
你认为他可以教我控制我的宇宙能量...
I could use it to find my sister?
好让我用它来找我的姐姐?
Maybe.
可能.
If that's what you want.
如果那是你想要的.
He's drained of Cosmo, Guraad.
他的宇宙血干了,古拉德.
Won't get another dose.
一剂也挤不出来了.
The prototype procedure has started.
原型程序已经开始.
It'll be ready tomorrow.
将在明天准备好.
Any issues?
有什么问题吗?
Just one.
只有一个.
Why Cassios?
为何是卡西欧斯?
'Cause you failed.
因为你失败了.
You know, the target was assisted by Alman Kido.
你知道的, 阿尔曼基多帮助目标.
A personal bad penny.
一个私人的不受欢迎人物.
Athena's growing stronger by the day,
雅典娜一天比一天强大
and now she'll have the Pegasus Knight by her side.
现在她有天马圣斗士在身边.
I reckon the boy's got some Cosmo. Doesn't mean he's a knight yet.
我想这男孩确实有宇宙能量.
I don't need cold comfort, Nero.
我不需要你的虚假安慰, 尼禄.
I need to know where on Earth Alman is hiding the girl.
我要知道阿尔曼把女孩藏在哪里...
So we can neutralize her before she becomes Athena
好让我们可以压制她...
Beats me.
帮不到你.
But you could always ask our prisoner.
但是你可以随时问我们的囚犯.
We have a prisoner?
我们有一个囚犯吗?
Hey!
嘿!
Hey, wait up.
嘿, 等一等.
Yeah?
什么事?
I... I just figured you could focus more on your training if you weren't
我想你可以更专注于你的训练
Thanks.
谢谢.
Seiya!
星矢!
Time to go.
是时候走了!
See you.
再见.
Take a seat.
坐下.
Don't get any big ideas.
别想多了.
Goddesses don't have boyfriends.
女神们没有男友.
-How many dads does Sienna have? -Buckle up.
-西耶娜有多少个爸爸? -扣上安全带.
Lunchbox?
午餐盒?
That's unusually kind of you.
你真是太好了.
I just thought he might as well enjoy his last meal,
我只是觉得他还不如享受他的最后一餐
since Marin's probably gonna kill him anyway.
反正马琳最终都会杀了他.
Right.
对.
So where am I supposed to go?
那我应该去哪里?
Okay. Just drop me off up there.
好, 放我在那里.
Not how it works.
不是这样的.
"Those who seek the master must do so on foot."
那些要寻找师傅的人必须靠走路.
What the hell am I doing here?
我在这里做什么?
I was wondering the same thing.
我也在想同样的问题.
You must be Marin.
你一定是马琳, 白银圣斗士.
No offense, I thought you'd be a man.
不是冒犯, 我以为你是个男的.
No offense taken.
我不介意. 我也是这么认为你.
I only train knights.
我只训练圣斗士.
I'm told I'm the Pegasus Knight.
有人说我是天马圣斗士.
You're not the first boy with a pretty necklace to show up here.
你不是第一个戴着漂亮项链来这里的人.
Is there a test I can take or something?
有没有一个测试来考验我?
The Pegasus Knight is brave.
天马圣斗士很勇敢.
Check.
有.
Humble.
谦虚.
And committed to protecting Athena with his life.
并誓死保护雅典娜.
Okay, that's where this whole situation gets a little sticky.
好, 这有点难说了.
See, I lost my sister-- Hey!
听好, 我失去我的姐姐...嘿!
I just got up here!
我刚上来这里!
I just got up here.
我刚上来这里.
I'm not going down there.
我不会下去那里.
There's nothing for you here.
-这里没有你要的东西. -你是什么, 忍者吗?
Listen, I only wanna find my sister. Sienna said you could help.
听好, 我只是要找到我的姐姐. 西耶娜说你能帮我.
I knew a knight just like you.
我认识一个很像你的圣斗士.
He desired power for his own goals.
他为自己的目标渴望力量.
-Which was? -The Phoenix.
谁?
You mean, aside from the Pegasus Knight.
你是说除了天马圣斗士?
I'll have Mylock come get you in the morning.
-我会叫迈洛克明早来接你. -不. 拜托, 我已经走了那么远.
And how far is that?
那你要多远?
Do you even know how far you need to go?
你知道你要走多远吗?
Just give me one chance.
给我一次机会.
If you can break this rock...
如果你能打破这石头...
then you can be my student.
那你就可以成为我的徒弟.
Fair enough.
好吧.
Where's the hammer?
锤子在哪里?
Come on, I can't break a rock with my bare hands.
我不能徒手破石头.
A knight could.
圣斗士可以.
You can't be serious.
你不是认真的.
I told you, this was stupid!
我说过这很愚笨!
Your flesh, this rock, the stars in the sky,
你的肉体, 这石头, 天空的星星...
all things in the cosmos are made from the same atoms.
宇宙万物来自同样的原子.
From the moment we are born, we all hold a Cosmo within ourselves.
从我们出生的那一刻, 我们内部都有宇宙能量.
A knight can make it explode.
一名圣斗士可以令它爆裂...
And shatter the atoms of any object.
粉碎任何东西的原子.
How's that supposed to make any sense?
怎么可能?
Focus.
专注.
Clear your mind.
理清你的思想.
Feel the Cosmo within you.
感受你内在的小宇宙.
Seiya!
星矢!
This is stupid, it'll never work!
真笨, 这永远做不到!
Something clouded your focus at the last minute.
有些东西在最后一刻模糊了你的专注.
Figures. Guess I'm not the Pegasus Knight after all.
很明显. 我想我毕竟不是天马圣斗士.
No, you're not.
你不是
But maybe you will be.
但是你会是.
Are you ready to start your training?
你准备开始你的训练了吗?
It's a good thing he didn't mind the permanent changes to his body.
好在他不介意身体的永久改变.
-Well... -What?
-瞧... -什么?
I might have forgotten to mention the permanent part to him.
我可能忘了提起永久那部分.
What the hell is this?
这是什么? 你做了什么?
You made me a freaking cyborg!
你把我变成了古怪机械人!
What is that?
那是什么?
It's the curse of Athena.
那是雅典娜的诅咒.
The war that awaits us is unlike any other before.
等着我们的战争不能跟以往相提并论.
Our enemies are the gods themselves.
我们的敌人是众神本身.
We've all made sacrifices.
我们都做出了牺牲...
But what is flesh in comparison to the power to crush the immortals?
但肉身与碾仙之力相比又算什么?
A war with the gods, huh?
与神对战吗?
There's only one person I wanna crush.
我只想砸一个人.
Well, that was a nice little show.
那是一个很好的表演.
Let's move on. We have bigger issues at hand.
忘记它. 我们手头上有更大的问题.
-Bigger than his ego? -Your prisoner.
-大过他的自大? -你的囚犯很坚定.
Let's get a baseline.
让我们看看你的基础.
Show me what you know.
让我看看你懂什么.
You mean, fight you? Now?
你是说和你战斗吗? 现在?
You came here to train, yes?
你是来训练的, 对吗?
Is dancing all you can do?
你只懂得跳舞吗?
Shouldn't I have a weapon or something?
我是不是应该有武器?
Athena's knights wield no weapon.
雅典娜的圣斗士不用武器.
That sucks.
真差劲.
Okay, I felt that one.
好, 我感受到.
It wasn't a direct hit.
那不是直接打击.
How the hell'd you do that?
你是如何做到的?
You want a weapon?
你需要武器吗?
Your Cosmo is your weapon.
你的宇宙能量就是你的武器.
Focus your energy,
专注你的能量, 让它在你体内燃烧.
Release it all at once.
然后像流星那样完全爆发出来.
Felt more like a meteor shower to me.
对我来说更像是流星雨.
So do I get to learn this meteor fist of yours?
那我可以学习你那流星拳吗?
You must...
你必须, 如果你想 在等待你的战斗中幸存下来.
Sienna!
西耶娜!
It's all right. It's all right.
没事.
I'm here. It's all right.
我在这里. 没事.
I had another vision. Bad one.
我看到另一个幻影. 很糟糕的幻影.
It's okay, it's all gone now.
没事, 现在没了.
Dad...
爸...
How can you be so sure I'll grow up to protect the world?
你怎么那么肯定我长大后会保护世界?
You are the goddess of wisdom, remember?
你是智慧女神, 记得吗?
And warfare.
还有战争.
And you're my baby girl.
而且你是我的宝贝女儿.
The most loving and stubborn.
最可爱和固执的.
Nothing could stop you from doing what's right.
没什么能阻止你去做正确的事.
What did you see?
你看到什么?
People... burning.
人们在燃烧.
Cities in ruins.
城市毁了.
Everything...
一切被摧毁了.
We won't let that happen, will we?
我们不会让那事情发生, 好吗?
You don't understand. It was Athena.
你不明白, 是雅典娜.
She was doing it. I...
是她在做. 我...
I was doing it.
我在做.
Visions are just... possibilities.
那幻影只是可能性.
Dad, I know you'd let the world burn to keep me safe...
爸, 我知道你会为了我而让世界燃烧...
but what if that's not me anymore?
但是如果那不再是我呢?
Prove to me you're worthy. Focus.
证明给我看你是值得的. 专注.
Is that all you've got?
那是你所有的本事吗?
Your body is here.
你的身体在这里...但是你的思想在别处.
Seiya.
星矢...
There's so many things I need to tell you.
我有很多东西要告诉你.
I'm here to protect you.
我是来保护你的.
Now stop my attack.
现在阻止我的攻击.
You're failing.
你快不行了.
Was he a knight too?
他也是圣斗士吗?
The Pegasus?
天马?
Mind and body must become one.
思想和身体必须合一.
You give up?
你投降了吗?
If you can't do this, you'll never be a knight.
如果你连这样都做不到, 你无法成为圣斗士.
You give up?
你投降了吗?
How did you say you ended up here, again?
你说你是如何沦落到这里了?
I didn't say. And it's none of your--
我没说过. 而且也不关你的...
Right, I'm not supposed to know. I know.
对, 我不应该知道. 明白.
My destiny is bound to this island.
我的宿命与这座岛息息相关.
Well, that sounds like a lonely existence.
那听起来很孤独.
But not one without purpose.
但并不是没有意义的.
You know, I...
你知道吗, 我...我也有一个目的.
To find my sister.
寻找我的姐姐.
A knight should not mistake obsession for purpose.
一名圣斗士不应将痴迷误认为是目的.
I know there is pain in your past...
我知道你的过去有痛苦...
but beyond that pain, there lies your strength.
但是在那痛苦后面就是你的力量.
Find it and the armor will accept you.
寻找它, 盔甲就会接受你.
This is what your sister would've wanted.
这是你姐姐想要的.
Get some sleep.
去睡吧.
I get it.
我明白.
You're tough.
你很强.
You know, someone once taught me
你知道吗...有一个人曾经教过我...
that all men, no matter how tough,
所有男人, 不管多强悍...
have something they fear.
都有他们恐惧的东西.
I wonder what it is a big man like you fears the most.
我在想像你这样的大个子会怕什么?
Who are you?
你是谁?
You have no idea what I'm capable of.
你不知道我的能力有多大.
Make it stop.
停止.
Make it stop!
停止!
Make it go away.
令它消失.
Now...
现在...
would you mind telling me where I can find Alman Kido?
可以告诉我要如何找阿尔曼基多吗?
Make it stop!
停止!
-This one's bigger than the last one. -And your Cosmo is stronger.
-这个比上一个大. -你的宇宙能量更强了.
Now, show me what you've learned.
现在让我看看你所学的.
You did it, Seiya.
你成功了, 星矢.
The Pegasus armor is--
天马盔甲是...
You can't use it. Only the Pegasus can.
你不能用它. 只有天马可以!
That's why you're coming with us.
所以你跟我们走.
Alman.
阿尔曼.
He was a part of it.
他是一份子.
He was there when Guraad took Patricia.
当古拉德带走派翠西亚时, 他在场.
I want off this island.
我要离开这座岛.
You are not ready.
你还没准备好.
Your training is not over.
你的训练还没结束.
It is now.
现在结束了.
Alman's been playing me for a fool!
阿尔曼一直在玩弄我!
You must calm down.
你必须冷静.
If your heart and mind aren't clear, the armor will reject you.
如果你的心灵不清, 盔甲会拒绝你.
To hell with the armor!
去他的盔甲!
Seiya.
星矢...
I don't care.
我不管!
You can either kill me now...
你要么马上杀了我...
or send me back.
要么送我回去.
Let's go. One more round, guys.
来吧. 再多一圈, 大伙们!
Come on.
来吧.
How's it coming along?
什么情况?
You want this to work, I need more time.
你要这个成功, 我需要更多时间.
Be careful, you idiot!
小心, 你这白痴!
Yeah, running out of sparring partners. You care to join?
是的, 没有对打对手了.
Oh, I'm sorry. Busy day.
抱歉, 我很忙.
Right, right. You're playing with your god-killing toy over here.
对.
Yeah.
是的.
So much trouble for one little girl.
那么麻烦来杀一个小女孩.
You know, if you ask me,
你知道吗, 如果你问我...
I'd be more than happy to snap her neck the old-fashioned way.
我很乐意以老方式扭断她的脖子.
Any damage to Sienna's body might awaken Athena's Cosmo within her.
西耶娜的身体如果受到破坏...
Yeah, I don't even know what that means.
是的, 我甚至不明白那是什么.
It means you can't dismantle a nuclear bomb by smashing it with a club.
这表示你不能用球棒来拆除核弹.
I'd sure love to try.
我倒很乐意尝试.
It's not happening.
这不可能发生.
Make it work.
把事情办成.
Alman!
阿尔曼!
I know what you did!
我知道你做了什么!
-Come face me, you coward. -Stand down!
-来面对我, 懦夫! -退下!
I'll handle this.
我来处理.
-Seiya, please. -Alman!
-星矢, 拜托. -阿尔曼!
Please calm down.
请冷静.
Stand back!
退下!
You can't hide from me.
你是躲不过我的!
Seiya!
星矢!
He took Patricia. He was in on it.
她捉了派翠西亚.
No! No, you don't wanna do that.
不! 你不想这样做.
You don't understand.
你不明白.
Come with me. I'll tell you what really happened to your sister.
跟我来. 我会告诉你姐姐的事.
Sienna, you know the rules.
西耶娜, 你知道规则!
You must not leave the mansion grounds.
你不能离开大宅的...范围.
You said you have answers.
你说你有答案.
Hey!
嘿!
Alman was there when Guraad took Patricia. He was a part of it.
当派翠西亚被古拉德捉走, 阿尔曼在场. 他是一份子.
Tell me I'm wrong.
告诉我错了.
He did it because of me.
他这样做是因为我.
When I was younger, I had no control at all.
当我还小的时候, 我完全无法控制.
One night, my mom was holding me and I had a burst of Cosmo.
有一晚, 我妈抱着我 然后我小宇宙爆发.
I don't even know how it happened.
我甚至不晓得它是如何发生的.
All I remember is she was holding me and I destroyed her arms.
我只记得她抱着我, 而我毁了她双手臂.
And the next moment, she was dying and it was all my fault.
下一刻, 她就垂死而且是我的错.
but ever since the accident, Guraad needs Cosmo to stay alive.
但是那次意外后, 古拉德需要宇宙能量来保命.
So what? You've got plenty of it.
那又如何? 你有很多.
Athena's Cosmo's too powerful. It would kill her.
雅典娜的宇宙能量太强了, 会害死她.
That's why she sought out kids like your sister.
所以她寻找像你姐姐的小孩.
What did she do to Pat?
她对派特做了什么?
Your sister didn't have any Cosmo.
你的姐姐根本没有小宇宙.
Once Guraad figured that out, she let her go.
一旦古拉德知道了, 她放过她了.
But she sent her men to watch her.
但是她派人盯住她.
Guraad knew Patricia was hiding something.
古拉德知道派翠西亚隐瞒一些东西.
Me.
我.
That's why she never came back.
所以她没有回来过.
Look, I'm sorry, Seiya. If I knew, I...
我很抱歉, 星矢.
My mother was never the same after the incident.
意外发生后, 我妈就跟以前不一样了.
She became convinced that Athena had returned to this world to end it.
她相信雅典娜是回来毁灭世界的.
She was gonna kill me, so my father forced me into hiding.
她要杀我, 所以我爸爸逼我躲起来.
And left Pat behind.
然后丢下派特.
Your sister wasn't the only one.
你姐姐并不是唯一一个.
We left them all behind.
我们把他们全都丢下.
How many kids did your family take?
你的家庭捉走了多少个孩子?
Our radar picked up Guraad's signature.
我们的雷达发现了古拉德的讯号.
So it is happening.
真的要发生了.
We don't stand a chance.
我们没机会.
You need to get out of here. I'll buy you as much time as I can.
你必须离开这里.
I'm not running from a fight.
我不会临阵退缩.
Find Sienna.
找西耶娜.
Protect her.
保护她.
You're the only one I can trust.
你是我唯一能相信的人.
And, Mylock?
迈洛克?
You've been a good friend.
你一直以来是个好朋友.
Thank you.
谢谢.
After Pat was taken, I ran away.
当派特被捉后, 我...我逃走了.
All these years, I've never stopped looking for her.
这些年来, 我从未停止寻找她.
Turns out she was the one who was keeping away from me.
结果是她要避开我.
Your sister sacrificed herself
你姐姐牺牲自己因为她相信真正的你.
I never asked to be a knight.
我从未想过成为圣斗士.
I only wanted to be with Pat.
我只想和派特一起.
You think I wanted any of this?
难道你以为我想要这一切吗?
Sometimes I feel like I'm a guest in my own body.
有时我觉得我只是这躯体的过客.
In time, I thought I'd learn to control it.
随着时间的推移, 我以为我学会控制它了.
But you're fighting it.
但是你在反抗它.
What if my mother was right?
如果我妈妈是对的呢?
What if I was only born to bring ruin and misery into this world?
如果我出生只会为这世界带来破坏和痛苦呢?
How do you know?
你怎么知道?
I guess I just know.
我想我就是知道.
I need you to promise me...
我要你答应我...
if things go wrong...
如果情况变糟...
if, in the end, I become a goddess of war and I can't control my powers...
如果, 到最后, 我成为战神和不能控制我的力量...
you will stop me, at all costs.
你要不惜一切代价阻止我.
-You don't mean-- -Just promise me, please.
你不是说...
That's my mother.
那是我妈妈!
Sienna, wait, you can't go back!
西耶娜, 等一等, 你不能回去!
-You're the one she's after. -I have to help my father.
-你就是她要找的人. -我必须帮我爸爸.
Okay.
好. 我和你去.
For now.
先这么办.
Shut it! Shut it!
关上!
Hold.
别动.
It's clear.
安全.
Where's Seiya?
西耶娜在哪里?
And whatever her name is?
不管她叫什么名字.
Sienna is not here, but I am willing to make a deal.
西耶娜不在这里, 但是我愿意谈条件.
Old man, you are in no position to be making deals.
老头, 你没资格谈条件.
Wait outside, Cassios.
外面等, 卡西欧斯.
-Are you serious? -Out!
-你说真的吗? -出去!
Hey!
嘿!
I really need to get to this ship.
我真的要登上这架飞机.
Glad you understand.
很高兴你明白.
How do you like my special bullets?
你喜欢我的特别子弹吗?
Let's make this easy, shall we?
让我们简化一下, 好吗?
Just tell me where she is.
告诉我她在哪里.
Straight to business, then.
那么开门见山吧.
What do you expect, after she almost killed me?
当她几乎杀了我过后, 你期待什么?
That was an accident and you know it.
那是意外, 你知道的.
You can't blame Sienna for it.
你不能怪西耶娜.
Oh, I never blamed Sienna.
我从未怪过西耶娜. 我怪你, 阿尔曼...
for leaving me to make all the hard choices.
让我做出所有艰难的选择.
How is murdering a little girl even a choice?
谋杀一个小女孩怎么会是一个选择呢?
She's a sword of Damocles hanging over all of us.
她是悬在我们所有人头上的剑.
-She's your daughter. -We never had a daughter!
-她是你的女儿! -我们从未有过一个女儿!
What we had was an agreement, remember?
我们有的是一个协议, 记得吗?
That when she'd go out of control, we'd do whatever had to be done together.
当她失控时, 我们会一起做该做的事.
Sienna was entrusted to me.
西耶娜被付托于我.
I'm responsible for her.
我要对她负责.
I believe in her.
我相信她.
You must believe in our child too.
你也必须相信我们的孩子.
Weren't you responsible for them?
难道你不需要对他们负责吗?
It was the only way to save you.
那是唯一救你的办法.
And now I must save the rest of us from her.
现在我必须把我们从她手中救出来.
Speaking of the devil.
说曹操, 曹操就到.
Dad?
爸?
I didn't want to do this, but I won't let you hurt her.
我不想这样做, 但是我不会让你伤害她.
I know.
我知道. 卡西欧斯!
Enough!
够了!
Get me the girl. You can do what you want with the boy.
捉那女孩给我. 你可以随意处置那男孩.
Seiya!
星矢!
We need to go.
我们必须走了!
Hey there. I'm gonna take the girl now.
嘿, 你好!
But first, I want you.
但是首先, 我要你.
Let's end this now.
我们现在来个了断吧.
-No, Seiya. Don't. -It's okay.
-不, 星矢, 不要. -没事.
I've got the armor.
我有盔甲.
Any time now.
现在任何时候.
Sienna, stay back!
西耶娜. 退后!
Things have changed, kid.
情况改变了, 孩子.
Face it, you don't have what it takes.
面对现实吧, 你根本不够格.
I loved these glasses.
我喜欢这副眼镜.
Stop! Stop!
住手!
You've won. I'm coming with you. Let him go.
你赢了, 我跟你走. 放过他.
You're coming with me anyway.
你无论如何都要跟我走.
Rescue on the way, kids.
救援马上就来, 孩子们.
I'm sorry,
对不起...
but I'm taking you down with me.
但是我要你陪我.
Go! Go! Go!
快走!
No.
不.
It's ready.
准备好了.
Give me a minute.
给我一分钟.
Leave.
出去!
You must think I'm the worst mother in the world.
你一定认为我是世界上最糟糕的母亲.
You... You killed Father.
你...你杀了爸爸.
Alman chose his own way,
阿尔曼选择他自己的路...
and left me to clean up his mess, as always.
留下我来收拾烂摊子, 像以前那样.
Athena's Cosmo is too strong.
雅典娜的小宇宙太强了.
It won't fix you.
它不适合你.
I know.
我知道.
Yeah. I gave up on fixing this body a long time ago.
是的. 我已经放弃修复这身体很久了.
We both have a bomb ticking inside.
我们俩体内都有一个计时炸弹...
Except yours is gonna be so much louder if we let it go off.
只是你的会更响...
I know I'm doing the right thing.
我知道我在做正确的事.
I just wanted you to know it doesn't make it any easier.
我只是要你知道这并不会令它更容易.
Will it hurt much?
会很痛吗?
I don't know.
我不知道.
We need to start.
我们必须开始了.
Do it.
动手吧.
Sienna...
西耶娜?
That ain't gonna help, kiddo.
那没帮助, 孩子.
I let her get taken.
我让她被捉走.
I failed.
我失败了.
We all did.
我们全都是.
I was supposed to protect her.
我应该保护她.
Come on, Seiya.
来吧, 星矢.
Marin.
马琳...
You were right about me.
你对我的评价是对的.
I failed.
我失败了.
I'm not a knight.
我不是圣斗士.
I couldn't save her.
我不能救她.
A knight should not mistake obsession for purpose.
圣斗士不应将痴迷误认为是目的.
Seiya, focus.
星矢, 专注.
Who is it that you're trying to save?
你到底想救谁?
Pat.
派特!
What does this...?
这是什么...?
Who are you really trying to save?
你到底想救谁?
I'm sorry.
对不起.
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉.
I know.
我知道.
It's okay.
没事.
It wasn't your fault.
这不是你的错.
Okay.
好.
I'll bring her back.
我会带她回来.
I promise.
我保证.
Okay.
好.
Let's go get Sienna back.
我们去救西耶娜回来.
How long will it take?
要多久?
To kill a god? Good question.
杀一个神吗? 好问题.
We're about to find out.
我们即将知道.
Oh, boy. They got us on radar.
天啊.
-What? -Get ready.
准备.
For what?
准备什么?
I can get you close, but I can't land.
我能送你去附近, 但不能降落.
Parachute?
降落伞呢?
Who says you're not funny?
谁说你不风趣?
It's now or never!
就是现在!
Open the doors.
开门.
Get yourself out of here!
你离开这里!
Godspeed, kiddo.
祝你一路顺风, 孩子.
-Out of the way. -Hey!
-让开! -嘿!
He's mine.
他是我的.
Big deal. You know how to glow.
有什么大不了, 你会发光.
Step aside, Cassios, if you don't wanna get hurt.
让开, 卡西欧斯, 如果你不想受伤.
Hurt?
受伤?
You should've died when you had the chance.
你应该趁还有机会就去死吧.
What was it that you said, Cassios?
你说什么了, 卡西欧斯?
Right.
对.
Oh, no.
糟了.
Things have changed.
情况改变了.
Finally, the goddess Athena reveals herself.
雅典娜女神终于露出真面目了.
You must believe in our child too.
你也必须相信你的孩子.
Stop! Stop the procedure!
停! 停止程序!
It'll be over soon.
即将结束.
Now!
现在!
We are not stopping!
我们不会停止!
Get out of my way.
让开.
Guards!
守卫!
Your services are no longer required.
现在不需要你的服务了.
There's no stopping it now.
现在不能停止了!
In moments, she'll be nothing but a memory.
转眼间, 她就只剩下回忆了!
Kill him!
杀他!
You said it yourself, Guraad.
你自己说过的, 古拉德.
When one goes to war with the gods, sacrifices must be made.
当一个人对神宣战...
There must be another way to protect humanity.
一定还有别的方法来保护人类!
Protect humanity?
保护人类?
Is that what you think you're doing?
这就是你以为你在做的吗?
Killing Athena was only half of the battle.
杀雅典娜只是战斗的一半.
This is the other half.
这是另一半.
The gold armor.
金盔甲.
Can't let you do that.
不能让你这样做.
Thought you were the only knight in town?
你以为你是唯一的圣斗士吗?
You gotta get out of the way.
你必须让开.
Sienna!
西耶娜!
You're no match for the Phoenix.
你不是暗黑凤凰的对手.
Why do you try so hard?
为何你那么努力尝试?
She's not worth it.
她不值得.
She's not even human.
她根本不是人类!
Sienna's not a god of war.
西耶娜不是战神.
Man needs no gods!
人类不需要神!
You don't know when to quit.
你不懂得什么时候投降.
People keep telling me that.
人们一直这样告诉我.
Stop, you fool!
住手! 你这笨蛋!
Sienna!
西耶娜!
Listen to me! That's not your friend anymore!
听我说! 那不再是你的朋友!
She's become the goddess of war.
她成为了战争女神!
We have to stop her!
我们必须阻止她!
Seiya.
星矢...
I'm losing control.
我失控了.
I don't think I can hold her back much longer.
我想我不能抑制她很久.
You can't save me,
你救不了我, 但是你可以阻止雅典娜.
You must do it now.
你必须马上做.
At all costs.
不惜一切代价.
Sienna...
西耶娜...
you're not a goddess of war.
...你不是战争女神.
No one's destiny...
没有一个人的命运是注定的.
Not even yours.
包括我们.
The guardian of mankind...
人类的守护者...
or a petulant jerk...
或一个任性的笨蛋...
whatever you choose to be, I'll never give up on you.
不管你选择成为什么, 我绝不会离弃你.
Seiya.
星矢...
What? Why?
为什么?
-What was that for? -Who's the petulant jerk?
-那是为了什么? -谁是那个任性的笨蛋?
-Get up. -Okay.
-快起来. -好.
Let's get out of here.
我们快离开这里.
Wait.
等一等.
I'm sorry.
对不起.
I was wrong about you.
我误会你了.
I wasn't so sure myself for a very long time.
很长一段时间我都不太确定自己.
You didn't have to do that.
你不必这样做.
Yes, I did.
是的, 我需要.
Did I do this?
这是我造成的吗?
Mylock!
迈洛克!
Sienna!
西耶娜!
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
I'm okay.
我没事.
Glad you made it, Seiya.
很高兴你成功了, 星矢.
You too.
你也是.
So, boss...
那么, 老板?
what do we do now?
我们现在要做什么?
Athena's awakening is a sign the old gods will soon return and try to start a war.
雅典娜的觉醒 预示旧神很快回归并试图发动战争.
We need to gather all the Knights of the Zodiac to stop them.
我们需要召集所有的十二宫骑士来阻止他们.
I'm at your service, my lord.
我随时为您效劳...
Stop. Don't call me that.
停止. 别这样叫我.
Whatever you say, princess.
随你怎么说, 公主.
Before we gather the knights, there's something else we need to do.
在召集骑士之前, 我们还需要做点别的事.
What's that?
什么事?
It's time to find Patricia.
是时候找派翠西亚了.
Thank you.
谢谢.
It's the least a goddess could do.
这是女神最起码能做到的.